

NILUPUL ISURUJITH

Software Engineer

About Me

I'm a self motivated, hard working person who loves to work with new technologies. My primary focus lies in mobile development, specializing in Flutter. I am enthusiastic about the opportunity to contribute my skills and passion to a dynamic team as a mobile developer.

- No:116,Godigomuwa, Ratnapura
- +94710380434
- nilupulisurujith96@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ni lupul-isurujith/
- https://github.com/Nilupul96

TECHNOLOGIES

- Dart
- Flutter
- Firebase

Familiar With

- Java
- React Native
- HTML
- PHP
- CSS

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Treinetic (Pvt) Ltd 2023 - 2024

Experienced software engineer proficient in developing 9+ projects using Flutter, specializing in cross-platform mobile application development. Skilled in integrating Firebase for backend services such as authentication, real-time database, cloud messaging, and analytics. Additionally, adept at integrating payment gateways such as Stripe, PayHere and implementing in-app purchasing functionalities. Experienced in deploying applications to both Android and iOS platforms.

ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Treinetic (Pvt) Ltd 2022 - 2023

TRAINEE SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Arimac Lanka (Pvt) Limited 2020

Worked as a mobile Developer on two projects. Technologies used - Flutter/ Bitrise/Microsoft Power Apps

PROJECTS

2023 Get In

Treinetic (Pvt) Ltd

Technologies-Flutter, Firebase, Payhere Payment Gateway

Ride-sharing application aimed at revolutionizing transportation solutions. This innovative platform connects passengers with drivers, fostering a collaborative environment to optimize travel efficiency with real-time tracking. I worked as one of the lead developers and was responsible for deploying iOS.





NON RELATED REFEREES

Mr Hashan Kannangara

Software Engineer
Treinetic (Pvt) Ltd
Tel:+94714431192
hashank@treinetic.com

Mr K.P. Sasindu Madushan

Software Engineer

DMS Software Engineering (Pvt)

Ltd

Tel:+94 716783018

sasindu@dmsswe.com

2023 **Slove**

Treinetic (Pvt) Ltd

Technologies-Flutter, QuickBlox Chat SDK, Stripe Payment Gateway

A platform that facilitates seamless connections between musicians and venues, optimizing the booking process and enhancing collaboration within the music industry.

2023 TOTT Mobile

Treinetic (Pvt) Ltd

Technologies-Flutter, Firebase

Specialized e-commerce application tailored for a single vendor, streamlining the process for customers to order items exclusively from their inventory. This user-centric platform offers an intuitive interface for seamless browsing and purchasing, ensuring a frictionless shopping experience.





2022 **VPN LIT**

Treinetic (Pvt) Ltd

Technologies-Flutter

This application offers users a secure and private internet browsing experience by encrypting their internet connection and concealing their IP addresses. Moreover, the app integrates Google AdMob and in-app purchases.





EDUCATION

Bsc (Hons) In Computing And Information Systems Sabaragamuwa University of Sri Lanka

2017 - 2022

G.C.E Advanced Level Examination

St. Aloysius College 2014

G.C.E Ordinary Level Examination

R/ Mihindu Vidyalaya 2011